http://www.milligazette.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The following information is provided to help you understand our policies.
The Milli Gazette / Pharos Media & Publishing Pvt LtdThanks for being part of our community! Use your browser's BACK button to return to the previous page when you are done here.Pharos Media has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy concerns of users of our site and to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. Except for the purposes set forth herein, Pharos Media will never sell or transfer your personal information to any unaffiliated person for any reason.Personal and Non-personal InformationWhen using our Web site, you may be asked to provide certain personal information about yourself for the purposes of purchasing, sending or redeeming a gift certificate, entering a contest, responding to a survey, etc. In general, Pharos Media will only use this information to comply with the purpose for which such information was requested. Pharos Media may, from time to time, use this information to send you information about new and exciting products and services offered by Pharos Media. Pharos Media will not share with or rent, sell or lease your personal information to any unaffiliated person or entity without your express consent. At any time you may revoke this consent by contacting us at the address provided below.We may also request and collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as gender, age, hobbies, or buying preferences. We may use this data to improve our site and to send you information that may be of interest to you. We may use this data to enhance your experience at our site, showing you content and promotional messages that we think you might be interested in, based on your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising on the Pharos Media Web site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person."Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with Web sites. Pharos Media may use cookies to customize your experience on the Pharos Media Web site. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, save your password (if you have registered with us) so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. You may, however, disallow receiving cookies at any time through your web browser. Pharos Media will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to the Pharos Media web site or your interaction with the Pharos Media Web site.We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you for the duration of a session and to gather broad demographic information.As you browse the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each Web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes called "clickstream" data, can be collected and stored by a Web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the Web site from which you linked to the Pharos Media Web site, and in some instances, your e-mail address. We may use clickstream data to determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our site and how they navigate throughout the Pharos Media site. We will only use this information to improve the Pharos Media Web site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any personal information.By providing any personal information to this site, users  fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information.Our site contains links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. Pharos Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.We may supplement the information that you provide to us with information that is received from third parties. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.Your Acceptance of this PolicyBy using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
